<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Daniel Tedman</title><link>https://tedman.dev/</link><description>As a Security Focused Software Engineer, I am committed to participating in the development of a
secure and accessible web.</description><atom:link href="https://tedman.dev/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Atkinson Hyperlegible</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/atkinson-hyperlegible/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/atkinson-hyperlegible/</guid><description>I am interested in contributing to making the web accessible to as many people as possible. When I heard about a project to design a typeface with the goal of increasing readability, I was interested in trying it out for myself.</description></item><item><title>Contributing to a Google Open Source Project</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/contributing-to-a-google-oss-project/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/contributing-to-a-google-oss-project/</guid><description>A chance encounter with a failing osv-scanner job, gave me the opportunity to contribute to a Google Open Source Project, learn more about Go, and help others avoid running into the same issue in the future.</description></item><item><title>Accretion (The Beginning)</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/accretion-the-beginning/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/accretion-the-beginning/</guid><description>Manage internal technical documentation that is enriched with live data accreted from your environment.</description></item><item><title>Go Homebrew Package</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/go-homebrew-package/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/go-homebrew-package/</guid><description>Go is an excellent language for writing command line tools, and Homebrew is the de facto package manager for macOS. This guide provides step by step instructions on how to get from go source code to published homebrew package.</description></item><item><title>Full Stack Faction</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/full-stack-faction/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/full-stack-faction/</guid><description>Product teams allow for cross-discipline collaboration, but can make it difficult for Developers to collaborate across the organisation with other Developers. The solution at my employer was the creation of a discipline specific guild called the Full Stack Faction.</description></item><item><title>Zero Downtime WordPress to Vue SPA &amp; Spring BFF Migration</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/zero-downtime-word-press-to-vue-spa-spring-bff-migration/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/zero-downtime-word-press-to-vue-spa-spring-bff-migration/</guid><description>An implemented proposal for how my team achieved zero downtime while migrating a WordPress website to a Vue SPA and Spring BFF in Kubernetes.</description></item><item><title>Embedding Content Within an Existing Site With PostCSS Prefix Wrap</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/embedding-content-within-an-existing-site-with-postcss-prefix-wrap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/embedding-content-within-an-existing-site-with-postcss-prefix-wrap/</guid><description>Embedding content within an existing site that you do not control, can be made possible with PostCSS Prefix Wrap, including third party libraries that you do not maintain.</description></item><item><title>Maintainable Legacy CSS With PostCSS Prefix Wrap</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/maintainable-legacy-css-with-postcss-prefix-wrap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/maintainable-legacy-css-with-postcss-prefix-wrap/</guid><description>Maintaining legacy CSS critical to support parts of your website that can not yet be upgraded, can be made maintainable with PostCSS Prefix Wrap, including third party libraries that you do not maintain.</description></item><item><title>A Reluctant Leader</title><link>https://tedman.dev/posts/a-reluctant-leader/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://tedman.dev/posts/a-reluctant-leader/</guid><description>I am a Software Engineer, not a Manager. This is the story I tell myself on a regular basis since being promoted to a Delivery Management role. Now, after more than one year in this role, it is time to reflect on my journey so far. To share my experience from the perspective of a reluctant leader.</description></item></channel></rss>